The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
♪ Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano ♪
The dreams I see are my secret
♪ Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano ♪
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
♪ Akai manto hira hira ♪
A red cape fluttering
♪ Uma o tobasu oujo ♪
Galloping on a horse—the princess
♪ Sore ga atashi ♪
That’s me!
♪ Lula-dula-lula-dula ♪
-
♪ Lulu laa, lulaa ♪
♪ Lula-dula-lula-dula ♪
-
♪ Lulu laa, lulaa ♪
♪ Ribon no kishi wa ♪
The Knight of the Ribbon,
♪ Honto wa hontto wa ♪
Truly, truly,
♪ Atashi nano sa ♪
It’s really me!
Thirty-First Episode
The Kingdom of the Seas
Tink and the Princess of the Sea
The sea is so vast and nice.
Put a baby turtle on the mama's back!
Put a little turtle on the mama's back!
Splash some water on them, splash, splash, splash!
That's so mean!
Wait!
Hey!
Come on, keep your head up!
Apologize and I'll forgive you!
Say something!
What was that?
You little runt!
Back off!
I'll punch you!
Fine by me!
All right!
What is it?
What's this?
Swish, swish, swish... And down!
Look, it's not much, but I earned this money tending sheep.
I'll give you this, so please let Kogame-san go.
Only ten yen?!
Don't underestimate me!
Hold still!
I'll take you down!
I don't think it's right to pick on the weak.
I-It spoke!
I don't think fighting is good.
I don't think it's right to bully the weak. I don't think it's right to bully the weak.
Come on, pull yourself together.
You know, I thought I'd save Kame-san
and his friends, just like Urashima Taro.
But it turned out the exact opposite.
I've been looking for someone like you.
Please save me!
Save you?
Come, off to the Dragon Palace!
The Dragon Palace?
Whoa, this is crazy!
I have no idea what's going on!
I told you, I can't swim!
Sapphire!
Tink!
Lord Sapphire, where are you going?
I'm going to play with Tink!
None of that matters!
Be that as it may, Lord Sapphire...
Tink!
Wait up!
I'm not Urashima Taro!
If I go to the Dragon Palace, I'll drown!
Please, just bear with it a little longer to help us out.
But the Dragon Palace is at the bottom of the sea, right?
I'm scared of the ocean floor.
Sapphire! Help me!
Oh! Is that where you were? Wake up! Hey, wake up! Come on, wake up!
Are you awake?
Is this... the place?
It's the Dragon Kingdom.
So we really are at the bottom of the sea.
But I'm not drowning...
Come on, let's go to the Dragon Palace!
The elders and the Sea God are waiting!
The Sea God?
That's right, the God of the Sea!
A god?
Sharks! Run!
Wait!
I hear it, I hear it!
A ship is passing overhead.
Hey, sharks! Drag that ship down here!
Maybe I can eat some crispy biscuits for a change.
Hey, turtle.
W-What is it?
What is that tiny human you've got with you?
T-This is my guest!
A guest?
Don't make me laugh.
Give it to me! No way!
Shut up!
The more I look at it, the cuter this human is.
I'll put it in my zoo.
Hand it over!
No!
Wait!
Hey, Anko.
A little turtle and a rare creature came by, didn't they?
I don't know!
Don't play dumb with me!
I'm going to search you.
Human food.
Biscuits.
Soggy, just as I thought.
Ah, so noisy! I can't even take a nap.
Help me!
Who's thrashing around inside my stomach?
Thank you.
You saved me.
And now my stomach hurts...
Come on, let's go to Dragon Palace.
Here it is.
Dragon Gate Castle is really run-down, isn't it?
It used to be grand.
It ended up like this because of those Sharks. That's right.
Great Sea God, we have guests!
We brought visitors!
Great Sea God!
Haven't I told you that yelling will break the castle?
Ah, welcome! Glad you're safe.
Hey, I thought Princess Otohime was at Dragon Gate Castle.
Princess Otohime is the Great Sea God's daughter.
Oh, so she really is here after all!
I'd love to meet her.
Princess Otohime isn't here.
Is she dead?
She's not dead!
It's just...
What's wrong?
I am Neptune, the Sea God.
Welcome, honored guest.
You seem like a kind-hearted person.
I'm Tink.
Tink, is it?
You certainly don't seem like an ordinary human.
You see...
Truth is, I'm not human.
I'm an angel.
Well, a former angel.
An angel?
Oh, what a blessing!
Sir Tink, please save my daughter, Otohime.
Save her?
What on earth happened?
Come this way, Sir Tink.
Right over here, Sir Tink.
Otohime is inside here.
Where?
I don't see anything.
Hey, is Ankou here?
Ankou!
Yes sir, right here!
Please give your consent.
Make it really bright, now!
That's a huge shell!
Princess Otohime has shut herself inside that shell and won't come out.
It's been a whole thousand years.
For a thousand years?
Why did she lock herself in?
Something terrible happened a thousand years ago.
Sir Tink, you are our last hope.
Please get my daughter out.
Kai-san, Kai-san, open your lid!
It's opening! It's opening!
Kai-san, Kai-san, open it wider!
No, close the shell!
Otohime, w-wait... Otohime, don't close it!
Don't close it!
Kai-san, Kai-san, please open up. The Sea God wants to see Lady Otohime.
Hey, open your shell!
What's wrong with the shell?
Won't you listen to me?
Close!
So, you're finally coming out.
I've been waiting for you, Otohime.
Otohime, Otohime, why won't you come out?
It's your fault.
Why are you meddling?
Get lost.
Shut up.
Now, where did he go?
Without Sapphire here, I'm hopeless.
Tink!
TINK!
Where could Tink have gone?
Feeling lonely, are we?
Shut up!
My, my, I am Lord Sapphire's escort—that is to say, his bodyguard.
You've got no right to tell me to shut up.
I don't need a bodyguard.
Stop following me.
As long as I trail behind,
I just might get the chance to
strike you down and send you to the next world.
Persistent and relentless—that's my best quality.
They say a turtle came to pick Tink up.
Yeah, he headed out toward the open sea.
Tink?
Lord Sapphire, where are you going in that beat-up boat?
I'm going to look for Tink!
Tink! Tink!
Talk about a stroke of luck!
That junk boat will sink before it even gets offshore.
This is the end for Sapphire! Ah, what bliss!
Tink!
Hey, hey! Let go of me!
Sharks, you promised you wouldn't get rough.
Yeah, well you're the one breaking your promise!
I'll keep my promise! I definitely, definitely will!
You mean it?
As promised a thousand years ago,
you'll give me Otohime as my bride, right?
Yes.
His bride?!
Yes, absolutely.
I really love Otohime.
So, when will she show up?
By the end of the day.
It's useless. I can't wait any longer.
I've waited a thousand years for this!
I'll drag Otohime out my own way.
Yes, I'll definitely do it.
Wait!
I'll be the one to summon Otohime.
Wait.
I can't wait any longer.
I'm doing this my way.
Got it?
That nuisance is gone.
Now, please bring her out this time.
No, I don't want her marrying someone like Sharks!
That Tink.
Lady Otohime.
You hid inside the shell because you didn't want to marry Sharks, right?
That's right.
But who are you?
I'm Tink.
I'll protect you, so don't come out no matter what!
Sir Tink...
A promise must always be kept.
Why did you make such a foolish promise?
To stop Shark's tyranny.
He swore he'd stop picking on the weak fish
if we gave him Otohime as his bride.
No way.
I'll never let them open that shell!
Sir Tink...
It's to protect the weak fish.
Please try to understand.
Hey, turtles!
Let's all protect Lady Otohime together!
That goes for the weak little fish, too, right?
That's right. Let's all fight together!
Tink doesn't know how terrifying the sharks are.
A ship is passing above.
That's right, sharks.
Drag the ship down!
And bring me some young maidens!
Yeah!
Tink!
I just hope Tink is alive.
I just hope she is alive... She's a perfect young maiden.
Now, the Pearl of Forgetfulness. Forget everything, and do as I command.
There we go. Now come along.
Now then, let the fashion show begin!
Young maiden,
put on the latest high-fashion dress and walk the runway.
It's Sapphire!
Wow, what a lovely outfit!
I'd love to show this to Otohime.
Ah, this is magnificent! The absolute best!
Buy 'em all!
Sapphire, I'm so glad you came.
Hey, Sapphire...
Stop it! Who are you?
Sapphire!
Don't just stand there, save Lady Otohime!
Sir Tink!
Where could he have gone?
Great Sea God, let's gather the fish and fight Sharks!
I'm afraid of fighting. Can't Sir Tink do something with his powers?
Otohime!
The wedding is about to start.
Got it?
You'll behave yourself once you're married, won't you, Sharks?
Well, who knows?
Father!
Otohime!
Fool!
What on earth happened?
- Giving up without a fight...
- I just don't get it.
What are you talking about?
No way! Who needs a Sapphire like this, anyway?
No, I hate you!
Tink!
It's Tink!
Why are we in a place like this?
Why?
It opened!
Come on, Tink!
Hurry up!
Hey, over here!
Here comes Her Highness the bride!
All right, let's begin.
Do you, Sharks, swear to take Otohime as your wife
and live in peace without causing trouble?
Well, I swear.
Otohime, living with Sharks as your husband may seem impossible,
but do you swear to endure it and live in peace?
Are you embarrassed?
Do you swear?
Answer already. I'm short-tempered.
Swear to me, my Otohime.
Come on, swear it!
Or else!
Hey, hold on!
Put up a good fight!
Take that!
You're only tough when picking on the weak!
Attack!
Charge!
Wow, way to go!
Oh, right!
Kai-chan!
Show your face!
Hurry, hurry!
Hey, I'm so glad I called you!
Sir Tink!
That was great!
Thank you, Sapphire, Tink!
I'm ashamed of myself!
I completely forgot about fighting!
What's wrong, Sapphire?
This is terrible!
In Urashima Taro,
one day in the Dragon Palace equals 50 years in the human world...
Yikes!
That means 50 years will have passed when we get back!
Don't worry!
Here, take this treasure box with you!
I'm sure it will come in handy!
The treasure box...
Goodbye!
Bye-Bye!
I'm so worried.
I wonder if all our friends have turned into old men by now...
Nylon!
What on earth happened?
Everyone is frozen!
What should we do?
I-I'm kind of scared...
Oh, I know!
Let me open the treasure box!
If we open it, smoke might puff out and turn us into white-haired old folks!
We haven't changed! What a relief!
Talk about a windfall!
Sapphire drowned at sea!
We'll make a fortune!
Look at that!
You two, I thought you were dead—what is going on here?
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen ♪
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
♪ Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen ♪
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
♪ Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo ♪
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
♪ tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai ♪
Our bonded hearts will never part.
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP